012global.com 2016-10-16

# 012Global | Low-Cost International Calls

1.   **012**  means 012Global Inc. a company established under the laws of Delaware, with its registered address at 7251 W palmetto park, Boca Raton, FL, USA

2.  This Privacy Policy explains how 012Global Inc ("012") collects, uses, and protects your information in relation to the 012Global Service ("the Service"). Please read this Privacy Policy before using the 012Global site ("the Site") and/or purchasing the Service. Please note that by using the Site and/or any part thereof, and/or by purchasing and/or using the Service, you represent that you have read this Privacy Policy, understood it, accepted it, and agreed to abide by its terms.

3.  You agree that any and all of the Information provided by you shall be accurate and truthful.

4.  Information 012 collect from you includes, but is not limited to, any of the following: name, postal address, phone number, e-mail address, and billing information ("the Information"). We may also survey you to understand more about your preferences concerning the Service.

5.  The following are the primary ways in which we collect the Information:  
\- You provide it to us (whether by using the Site or in conversation with our representative);  
\- We collect it automatically when you use the Site and/or use the Service;  
\- We obtain it from other sources, such as advertise agencies.

6.  012global uses information collected from your use of the 012global platform or Websites or any of 012global services to analyze trends, administer the use of the platform, 012global Websites or any of 012global services, provide customer support, enforce the Agreements, resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems, customize, measure, and improve the platform, 012global Websites or any of its services its content or layout; inform you about targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers unless you opt out; compare information for accuracy, and verify your identity; and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use

7.  Choice/Opt-out . 012 users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to 012 Websites, platform or services. In order to unsubscribe you may send an email to support@012global.com and your request will be recorded on our database.

8.  Any information collected by 012global, including without limitation, your Personal Data or information collected your use of 012global Websites or platform or any services provided by 012global, may be stored and processed in any country, at 012global sole discretion. By using the platform or any of 012global Websites or any service provided by 012global, you consent to any transfer of information outside of your country, or from any other country to any other country, at 012global sole discretion.

9.  Offered by us or by our affiliates, without disclosing your personal information to our affiliates. We may also at any time disclose any of the Information:  
(i) pursuant to any legal demand from a competent authority, and  
(ii) to third parties relevant to provision and/or your use of the Service (in which events you will not necessarily receive notification of such disclosure, and you agree that you will not have any claim and/or demand with relation to such disclosure and/or lack of notification thereof).

10.  In the event that 012 will acquire additional companies as subsidiaries, or will be bought by another company, the personal data collected will generally be one of the business assets transferred.  
We reserve the right to transfer personal data with such transaction as a part of our business assets.

11.  We will not use and/or disclose the Information other than as expressly permitted in this PRIVACY POLICY.

12.  The Site may contain links to other sites the information practices of which may be different from those of 012.  
If you enter such site through such a link, We advise that you consult the privacy policy of the site, as We have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, such site.  
Please note that this PRIVACY POLICY may be revised from time to time, and you are requested to check it from time to time.  
At any point in time, the current version then posted on the Site is the applicable version.
